Class of 1993 Records, 1989-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1993 Records
1989-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1993.
RG 80 UUID:a0860989-0f28-4f50-a290-994a25fbcbae
4 boxes (3.33 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1993.
The Class of 1993 was the 115th graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1993 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1993, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1993 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General 1989-1995 (Box 2303, Folder 1)
- Ada Comstock Scholars Photo Book 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 2)
- Class Rep List 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 3)
- Commencement 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 4)
- Ivy Day 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 5)
- Last Chapel 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 6)
- Reunion Newsletter 1998-2003 (Box 2303, Folder 7)
- Senior Ball 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 8)
- Sophomore Push 1991 (Box 2303, Folder 9)
- Who's Who 1989-1990 (Box 2303, Folder 10)